放开他
云霄哥你怎么来了
我们只是帮他练练舞耶
我胸子扎这么多
我那是我妈在车里等你
我们走
没事吧要不要去医务室看一下
谢谢但是太贵重了
是你你记不记得明周快点回家了
啊你怎么进来了
少爷先上车吧
这孩子东西落下你都不知道
装可怜
好让云中溪等你
我没有你这种女孩我见得多了
我警告你
离我儿子远点
我心目中的儿媳
只能是小巷
等等武邪
等等等等
Let him go!
Brother Yunxiao, why are you here?
We're just helping him practice dancing
My chest is tied so much
I'm my mom waiting for you in the car
Here we go.
Are you alright? Do you want to go to the infirmary to take a look?
Thank you, but it's too expensive.
It's you, do you remember to go home soon tomorrow week?
Ah, how did you get in?
Master, get in the car first
You don't even know this kid left something behind
Pretend to be poor
So that Yunzhongxi can wait for you
I don't have a girl like you I see a lot
I warn you.
Stay away from my son
My daughter-in-law
Only alleys
Wait Wu Xie
And so on.